<vn>
	<!-- Characters -->

	<character id="pessy">
		<name>Pessy</name>
		<image>pessy</image>
		<scale>1</scale>
		<color>653BA9</color>
		<side>left</side>
	</character>

	<character id="cody">
		<name>Cody</name>
		<image>cody</image>
		<scale>1</scale>
		<color>A36BCC</color>
		<side>right</side>
	</character>

	<character id="gaysex">
		<name>Pessy &amp; Cody</name>
		<image>kiss</image>
		<scale>1</scale>
		<color>7c4cb6</color>
		<side>center</side>
		<offset>0,50</offset>
	</character>

	<!-- Dialogue -->
<entry id="start" bg="school">
	The day starts of as usual, with Cody and Pessy meeting each other whilst on the way to school
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Hey Cody! How are you doing?
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Hey Pessy, I'm doing well!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Did you sleep well Cody?
	<choice id="sleepyes">Yes i did</choice>
	<choice id="sleepno">No i didn't</choice>
</entry>

<entry id="sleepyes" character="cody" bg="school">
	I slept well, I dreamt about all the possibilities of what Friday Night Funkin' could include in their next update!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I imagine what the lemon demon songs for the erect difficulty would sound like!
</entry>


<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Oh yeah!! I bet it's gonna sound really creepy but also good!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="talk-current-mods">
	I bet. The voice actor for him is really good at it!
</entry>

<entry id="sleepno" character="cody" bg="school">
	I had a horrible nightmare, I dreamt of Friday Night Funkin' getting canceled.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	It was due to the developers being exposed of spending all the kickstarter money on crack. A team member who is against this posted a google doc of the situation on twitter.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Oh man that must have been a really bad nightmare. At least they are now showing teasers online like that erect sampler they showed the other day!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="talk-current-mods">
	Yeah, I'm really glad that they are now finally doing that after almost 3 years of nothing. The FNF mods were really making this community alive.
</entry>


talk about current mods, where each engine talking about each others engines mods and how cool they are

<entry id="talk-current-mods" character="cody" bg="school">
	Have you heard about the mod…

	<choice id="talkimpostor">Talk about: Impostor V4</choice>
	<choice id="talkhotline">Talk about: Hotline 024</choice>
	<choice id="talkmario">Talk about: Mario's Madness</choice>
	<choice id="talk17">Talk about: 17 Bucks</choice>
</entry>

<entry id="talkimpostor" character="cody" bg="school">
	Vs Impostor?
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yea i heard about that! I find it very sus! Ha.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	But actually it's a really good mod. I like how Maroon's parasite form looks! It really fits for his song.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Yeah me too!! My favorite part from Vs Impostor is Finale. That song is so good I love it to death!!!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	I don't blame you! That's the best song from the mod tbh.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Have you heard about Sunday's Desolation?
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Oh yeah I did! That's such a good mod. It's really high quality for a fanmade mod about Wednesday's Infidelity!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yeah, it even has one of your developers for your engine on the team. That's really awesome!!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="fnfstuff">
	I think that's really cool actually. I like that this mod is all about Oswald from the original mod. Really cool that the team is making a whole mod about him!
</entry>

—-

<entry id="talkhotline" character="cody" bg="school">
	Hotline 024?
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yea i heard about that! I really like Nikku's character design, and how she can mimic other voices!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Yeah!! There's even a whole tricky-themed song in the mod, and even Nikku is mimicking Tricky's voice at certain parts!!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Kinda sucks that the original tricky mod was made on Kade Engine, Kevin is just really too much of a hardcoding guy and he is really unoptimized. I don't like talking to him that much.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I do see him hanging out with the other engines. But lately his popularity has kinda stopped.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yeah… I do admit he's the reason why people started modding FNF though, he's the one that started FNF modding!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I agree… He actually makes me feel nostalgic of the early era of FNF modding…
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Have you seen Cyber Sensation recently?
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I did actually! Unfortunate that it got canceled though…
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school" next="fnfstuff">
	Yeah… the creator had to leave the community. Got exhausted from the game.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I don't blame her. FNF does get really tiring after a good while.
</entry>

—---

<entry id="talkmario" character="cody" bg="school">
	Mario's Madness?
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yeah! That's one of the trending mods right now! I like how All-Stars play out. It's such a sad but awesome ending!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I agree!! Some people are mad about it, but to be honest BF wins too much. He had to lose at some point.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	True. Sometimes all good things must come to an end.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	heyy mmv2 reference!! That's from the dialogue when mario sees bf again before All-Stars happens lol!!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	omg LMAO cody you're so funny!!!
</entry>

<entry bg="school">
	They laughed for a solid 5 minutes.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	haha….. Anyways, did you hear about Gorefield getting a big update?
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Yeah I did!! V2 is such a huge improvement from V1 it's insane.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yeah!! I like how Cataclysm goes… It's pretty similar to All-Stars
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	It's a really awesome song to be honest!! Such an awesome ending to the mod. I like that there are flashbacks of the previous songs played and that they are being controlled by Godfield.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Again, it's like how All-Stars play out! Like how Ultra M is controlling the past enemies the player faced against at Act 4.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="fnfstuff">
	I really like that mods do that.
</entry>

—---


<entry id="talk17" character="cody" bg="school">
	17 Bucks?
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yeah I have! The charm of it is actually so amazing.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I agree, my favorite song from the mod is Kevinteenbucks.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Cool! Mine is Fitin'. The song loops forever but to be honest that's really funny to me!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I think that's funny too! That's actually my first time seeing a mod do that when I first played it.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yeah, it's pretty awesome! Pretty cool how people in this community can code such cool things.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Have you heard about YTP Invasion?
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Yeah!! It's not out yet, but it's going to really soon!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yup.. I think it's gonna drop this month actually!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Whaaat, really??
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yes, they announced that sometime ago on their twitter account! They released a trailer about it and everyone got super hyped about it!!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Woahhh… cool!! What is it all about?
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Well basically, it's a mod about iconic Youtube Poop (YTP for short) characters rap battling against boyfriend.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="fnfstuff">
	Sounds cool! I think that's gonna be a really awesome mod everyone will love.
</entry>

—---


talk about some stuff that's been happening with the base game

<entry id="fnfstuff" character="cody" bg="school">
	Did you see that new FNF blog that recently got released? It shows the new chart editor that's with the base game!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	I saw!!! It looked really cool. I saw it looked inspired by your editor.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I know! It feels inspired by yours too!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yeah! I rembeber adding waveforms way back! Also they added your note selection and dragging!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	That just makes me really happy. Even though I'm not that much of a popular engine, the FNF developers still might have taken some inpriation from me. Which is awesome considering they defenitely took some from you!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	That shows they take advice from FNF modders and FNF engine developers! They care about the community.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	That may be true because they also updated their erect songs after dropping the erect sampler!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	They did? Wow! That's actually really awesome. What songs did they change?
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	So far we only know Fresh and Pico. They dropped the updated versions on their Tiktok account.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Oh cool! I didn't really like how BF sounded in Pico. His vocals were kinda just all over the place.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Yeah they actually changed that! His vocals became less intense and are actually more calm now.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school" next="personaltalk">
	That's awesome. I really can't wait for the update!
</entry>

—-

small personal talk

<entry id="personaltalk" bg="school">
	The both of them start thinking about their personal things. Both of them think they should share it to the other.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I recently transitioned from alpha to beta state the other day.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Oh really? That's great news! Good job on making progress on your engine!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Thank you! I'm actually excited to release this engine at some point.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I also heard that you started working on the final version of psych. That's pretty cool!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	I heard it's gonna have a stage editor! I'm really excited to see that!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Yea and I'm also working on adding Language support, and a new chart editor.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
    Oh awesome!! That's cool that you're finishing your engine. I can't wait for it to drop!
</entry>

<entry bg="school" next="crush">
    They both went silent for a moment.
</entry>

—--

talking about crushes

<entry id="crush" character="pessy" bg="school">
	I have a crush on this engine where you can softcode literally anything…
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	R…really? Who is this engine you're talking about…?
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	…Y-...you…
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	…W-what? Oh my god… I think I'm blushing…!!
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	…yeah…
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	…well…

	<option id="crushaccepted">Tell Pessy your feelings for her</option>
	<option id="friendzone">I don't feel the same way</option>
</entry>

<entry id="crushaccepted" character="cody" bg="school">
	I have a crush on an engine that is user-friendly and has lua scripting…
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	…Cody…
</entry>

<entry bg="school">
	Pessy leans to Cody for a kiss.

	<choice id="kiss">Kiss Pessy</choice>
	<choice id="no-kiss">Reject the kiss</choice>
</entry>

<entry id="kiss" bg="school">
	Cody leans to Pessy to kiss her.
</entry>

<entry character="gaysex" bg="school">
   *muwha* *sloppy kisses*
</entry>

<entry character="gaysex" bg="school">
   *drools* *muwah muah*
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
   …that… was something.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
   Cody… I love you.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
   …I… love you too…
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
   …
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="ending">
   …
</entry>

<entry bg="school" next="ending">
	Pessy looks at her clock. It seems they are running late for class!
</entry>


<entry id="no-kiss" bg="school">
	Cody backs up.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Hey wait… I don't really wanna start this relationship yet.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Oh… well that's alright. Do you wanna have a date sometime later then?
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="ending">
	Sure. I think we gotta develop our feelings for each other first before we take it to the next level.
</entry>

<entry bg="school" next="ending">
	Pessy looks at her clock. It seems they are running late for class!
</entry>


<entry id="friendzone" character="cody" bg="school">
	…Pessy… I really don't want to hurt your feelings, but I don't feel the same way for you…
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Oh… well… I'm sorry for being weird there…
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	It's ok Pessy… I think it's best if we just stay as friends.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Alrighty… I'm ok with that.
</entry>

<entry bg="school" next="ending">
	Pessy looks at her clock. It seems they are running late for class!
</entry>

—

ending

<entry id="ending" character="pessy" bg="school">
	We should probably get to class now!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	It was really fun talking to you.
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Same here.
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school">
	Well I will see you sometime later, ok?
</entry>

<entry character="pessy" bg="school">
	Alrighty… Bye Cody!!
</entry>

<entry character="cody" bg="school" next="credits">
	Bye Pessy!
</entry>

Credits:

<entry id="credits" bg="school">
	Credits:
	Coding: Ne_Eo
	Music &amp; Sfx: Bromaster819
	Writing: Syrup, Bromaster819, Ne_Eo, SlightlyCreative, swordcube
	Art: Mkv8
</entry>

<entry bg="school">
	Time spent writing this novel: 3h 19m
	Time since idea: 3h 57m
</entry>

<entry bg="school">
	Replay?

	<choice id="start">Yes</choice>
	<choice id="exit">Exit</choice>
</entry>


</vn>